I feel like May Day growing up was just us like walking around a pole with ribbons.
Remember that? I did not know about May Day being an international day that is basically Labor Day
for the globe. It was created basically because of the hay market affair that took place in 1886
in Chicago. There was a peaceful protest that was taking place where laborers were peacefully
protesting for an eight-hour workday and of course the police came through and do what the police be
doing and shit turned up and an explosive went off and here we go there we go. It was not
a good scene. However people say that this actual incident really set the stage for big changes to
happen in the labor movement. America and Canada decided that Labor Day would be the first Monday
of September. However this other organization Organization of Socialist Labor Parties they
said no it's gonna be May 1st and internationally May Day became a day for unions worldwide to
demonstrate. Now I say all that to say that on this May Day it could be worth watching this
documentary AmeriKond which speaks to not only the necessity for labor unions but the ways in which
America does not support laborers in this country. Honestly it just never ceases to amaze me how much
we don't know about how whack this country is. Happy May Day. May Day! May Day! Democracy Overboard!
That was cheesy but I had to do it. It was right there.